{
    "subject": "resource/Pinnacle_Studio",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Pinnacle Studio is a video editing program originally developed by Pinnacle Systems as the consumer-level counterpart to Pinnacle's former professional-level software, Liquid Edition. It was acquired by Avid and later  by Corel in July 2012.",
    "human_readable": "Pinnacle Studio's comment states that it is a video editing program originally developed by Pinnacle Systems as the consumer- level counterpart to Pinnacle's former professional-level software, Liquid Edition, which was acquired by Avid and later by Corel in July 2012.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9341689348220825,
            "question": "What was the name of Pinnacle's former professional-level video editing software?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9112869501113892,
            "question": "Who originally developed Pinnacle Studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8469279408454895,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Pinnacle Studio and Liquid Edition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8304077386856079,
            "question": "What type of software is Pinnacle Studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.802112877368927,
            "question": "What is the purpose of Pinnacle Studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7996591925621033,
            "question": "Can you name a feature commonly found in video editing software like Pinnacle Studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6810737252235413,
            "question": "When did Corel acquire Liquid Edition?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6359803676605225,
            "question": "Is Pinnacle Studio still in development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6310035586357117,
            "question": "What was the target audience for Pinnacle Studio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6251479387283325,
            "question": "Which company acquired Liquid Edition?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pinnacle Studio's comment states that it is a video editing program originally developed by Pinnacle Systems as the consumer- level counterpart to Pinnacle's former professional-level software, Liquid Edition, which was acquired by Avid and later by Corel in July 2012.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3194_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the target audience for Pinnacle Studio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3194_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Pinnacle Studio still in development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3194_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Corel acquire Liquid Edition?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3194_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3194_82.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the statement that Pinnacle Studio's comment states that it is a video editing program originally developed by Pinnacle Systems as the consumer-level counterpart to Pinnacle's former professional-level software, Liquid Edition, which was acquired by Avid and later by Corel in July 2012. This statement is directly supported by the text from file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3194/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information that supports the statement about Pinnacle Studio being a video editing program originally developed by Pinnacle Systems as a consumer-level counterpart to their professional software, Liquid Edition. They also mention its acquisition by Avid and then Corel in July 2012."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}